<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Star Wars Canon Tracker</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_media_list">Canon List</string>
    <string name="nav_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="sync_online">Sync database now</string>
    <string name="media_title">Title</string>
    <string name="media_type">type</string>
    <string name="watched_read">Completed</string>
    <string name="want_to_watch_read">Wishlist</string>
    <string name="owned">Owned</string>
    <string name="nav_subtext">Do or do not.</string>
    <string name="launcher_icon_description">Launcher Icon</string>
    <string name="copyright_notice">This app is in no way affiliated with or endorsed by Disney or Lucasfilm. I do not claim to own Star Wars or any of its related copyrights or trademarks. The use of Star Wars content in this app is protected under Fair Use.</string>

    <string name="welcome_message">Welcome to the Star Wars Canon Tracker app. I hope it is to your liking.
        Click on "Settings" in the navigation to change the text for the checkboxes and to permanently filter out
        certain media types.</string>
    <string name="nav_about">About This App</string>
    <string name="current_database_version">current database version</string>
    <string name="update_0_1_6">Version 0.1.6: Now restricts downloading of data to unmetered networks only. This feature can
    be turned off in the settings.
    Some small modifications were made to the layout of the list items. Namely I made the thumbnail a little bigger and stopped long titles from crashing into the checkboxes.</string>
    <string name="update_0_1_5">Version 0.1.5: Some more stability fixes.
    There was a crash involving clicking on a media item and opening the page for that item that should be fixed.
    Images should load much smoother now.
        Plans for the coming updates: remembering filters, wifi-only downloading of database and images, updating database.
        Don\'t forget to leave feedback or e-mail me through the play store entry so I know what else can be done to improve the app.
    </string>
    <string name="update_0_1_4">Version 0.1.4: This update should improve stability (i.e. the app shouldn\'t crash so much anymore).</string>
    <string name="update_0_1_0">Version 0.1.0: Initial release! Hooraaaay!
        I\'m still working on fixing up release dates, images, and timeline in the database.
        It should automatically update when I do that.
        This app downloads the database and images, so try not to use it without wifi for now.
        Future versions will have an option to not download unless on wifi.</string>
    <string name="cover_image_description">cover</string>
    <string name="wifi_sync_setting">sync_wifi_only</string>
</resources>
