<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE resources [
    <!ENTITY appname "HoloCanon">
    ]>


<resources>
    <string name="app_name">&appname;</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_media_list">Canon List</string>
    <string name="nav_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="sync_online">Sync database now</string>
    <string name="media_title">Title</string>
    <string name="media_type">type</string>
    <string name="checkbox1_default_text">Completed</string>
    <string name="checkbox2_default_text">Wishlist</string>
    <string name="checkbox3_default_text">Owned</string>
<!--    <string name="nav_subtext">Do or do not.</string>-->
    <string name="nav_subtext">This is the way.</string>
    <string name="launcher_icon_description">Launcher Icon</string>
    <string name="copyright_notice">This app is in no way affiliated with or endorsed by Disney or Lucasfilm.
        I do not claim to own Star Wars or any of its related copyrights or trademarks.
        The use of Star Wars content in this app is protected under Fair Use.</string>

    <string name="welcome_message">Welcome to &appname;, an unofficial canon tracker for the Star Wars universe.
        Click on "Settings" in the navigation to change the text for the checkboxes and to permanently filter out
        certain media types. Come find me on twitter <a href="https://twitter.com/holocanon">@HoloCanon</a>.
        I\'ve also got a <a href="https://discord.gg/RxXvTfX">Discord server</a> set up, which would be a great way to make suggestions or report bugs for this app.
        Additionally, if you have any bugs, requests, or corrections, you can e-mail me at <a href="mailto:DarthMerman@gmail.com">DarthMerman@gmail.com</a>.</string>
    <string name="affiliate_notice">As an Amazon Associate I may earn money from qualifying purchases made through the links in this app.</string>
    <string name="nav_about">About This App</string>
    <string name="current_database_version">current database version</string>
    <string name="update_1_0_2">Version 1.0.2: Changed app name to better comply with Google Play\'s rules.
        Cleaned up the individual item layout so the descriptions and reviews (that I\'m working on adding) show up cleanly.</string>
    <string name="update_1_0_1">Version 1.0.1: Added links to purchase items from Amazon to the canonical items pages.
    Using these links to purchase things will help support this app. Also changed the color of the sort/filter buttons.</string>
    <string name="update_1_0_0">Version 1.0.0: First full release.</string>
    <string name="update_0_1_6">Version 0.1.6: Now restricts downloading of data to unmetered networks only. This feature can
    be turned off in the settings.
        Updating is now also done silently in the background unless forced from the settings menu.
    Some small modifications were made to the layout of the list items. Namely I made the thumbnail a little bigger and stopped long titles from crashing into the checkboxes.
    0.1.6b: Fixed a crash that occurred when trying to view a media item that doesn\'t have a downloaded thumbnail. Also added this update text.</string>
    <string name="update_0_1_5">Version 0.1.5: Some more stability fixes.
    There was a crash involving clicking on a media item and opening the page for that item that should be fixed.
    Images should load much smoother now.
        Plans for the coming updates: remembering filters, wifi-only downloading of database and images, updating database.
        Don\'t forget to leave feedback or e-mail me through the play store entry so I know what else can be done to improve the app.
    </string>
    <string name="update_0_1_4">Version 0.1.4: This update should improve stability (i.e. the app shouldn\'t crash so much anymore).</string>
    <string name="update_0_1_0">Version 0.1.0: Initial release! Hooraaaay!
        I\'m still working on fixing up release dates, images, and timeline in the database.
        It should automatically update when I do that.
        This app downloads the database and images, so try not to use it without wifi for now.
        Future versions will have an option to not download unless on wifi.</string>
    <string name="cover_image_description">cover</string>
    <string name="setting_unmetered_sync_only">sync_wifi_only</string>
    <string name="release_date">release date</string>
    <string name="bundleItemId">item Id</string>
    <string name="update_1_0_3">Version 1.0.3: Filters and sorting method should now persist when you return to the Canon List.
        I also changed some things under the hood, so if the app seems to be running slower or something isn\'t working as expected, then let me know (through my twitter/discord/e-mail, all listed above).</string>
    <string name="update_1_0_4">Version 1.0.4: Added a series page for relevant items, which can be accessed through any item in that series.
        This means can now check off the entire Clone Wars series at once (hooray!).
        Changed the filter selection menu which should allow for better control over filters.
        Also added series filtering (let me know if there are any discrepancies or missing series).</string>
    <string name="description_header">Description: </string>
    <string name="review_header">My Review: </string>
    <string name="series_title">series title</string>
    <string name="series_image_description">series image</string>
    <string name="view_series">View Series</string>
    <string name="nav_filters">Filters</string>
</resources>
